http://www.hydrogencarsnow.com/index.php/terms-of-service/

Breaking News
Toyota & Iwatani Creating 7 New Hydrogen Fueling Stations in California
Terms of Service
In using the HydrogenCarsNow.com website you are deemed to have read and agreed to the following terms of service and conditions:
The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and any or all Agreements: “Client”, “You” and “Your” refers to you, the person accessing this website and accepting the Company’s terms and conditions. “The Company”, “Ourselves”, “We” and “Us”, refers to our Company, HydrogenCarsNow.com. “Party”, “Parties”, or “Us”, refers to both the Client and ourselves, or either the Client or ourselves. All terms refer to the offer, acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner, whether by formal meetings of a fixed duration, or any other means, for the express purpose of meeting the Client’s needs in respect of provision of the Company’s stated services/products, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing English Law. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalisation and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.
Privacy Statement
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Authorized employees within the company on a need to know basis only use any information collected from individual customers. We constantly review our systems and data to ensure the best possible service to our customers. Parliament has created specific offences for unauthorised actions against computer systems and data. We will investigate any such actions with a view to prosecuting and/or taking civil proceedings to recover damages against those responsible
Confidentiality
We are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 and as such, any information concerning the Client and their respective Client Records may be passed to third parties. However, Client records are regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, other than if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities. Clients have the right to request sight of, and copies of any and all Client Records we keep, on the proviso that we are given reasonable notice of such a request. Clients are requested to retain copies of any literature issued in relation to the provision of our services. Where appropriate, we shall issue Client’s with appropriate written information, handouts or copies of records as part of an agreed contract, for the benefit of both parties.
We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by this Company will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products. See our Privacy Policy page for more details.
Disclaimer
Exclusions and Limitations
The information on this web site is provided on an “as is” basis. To the fullest extent permitted by law, this Company:
excludes all representations and warranties relating to this website and its contents or which is or may be provided by any affiliates or any other third party, including in relation to any inaccuracies or omissions in this website and/or the Company’s literature; and
excludes all liability for damages arising out of or in connection with your use of this website. This includes, without limitation, direct loss, loss of business or profits (whether or not the loss of such profits was foreseeable, arose in the normal course of things or you have advised this Company of the possibility of such potential loss), damage caused to your computer, computer software, systems and programs and the data thereon or any other direct or indirect, consequential and incidental damages.
This Company does not however exclude liability for death or personal injury caused by its negligence. The above exclusions and limitations apply only to the extent permitted by law. None of your statutory rights as a consumer are affected.
Termination of Agreements and Refunds Policy
Both the Client and ourselves have the right to terminate any Services Agreement for any reason, including the ending of services that are already underway. No refunds shall be offered, where a Service is deemed to have begun and is, for all intents and purposes, underway. Any monies that have been paid to us which constitute payment in respect of the provision of unused Services, shall be refunded.
Availability
Unless otherwise stated, the services featured on this website are only available within the United States, or in relation to postings from the United States. All advertising is intended solely for the United States market. You are solely responsible for evaluating the fitness for a particular purpose of any downloads, programs and text available through this site. Redistribution or republication of any part of this site or its content is prohibited, including such by framing or other similar or any other means, without the express written consent of the Company. The Company does not warrant that the service from this site will be uninterrupted, timely or error free, although it is provided to the best ability. By using this service you thereby indemnify this Company, its employees, agents and affiliates against any loss or damage, in whatever manner, howsoever caused.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Additionally, for systems administration, detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes, our web servers automatically log standard access information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL. This information is not shared with third parties and is used only within this Company on a need-to-know basis. Any individually identifiable information related to this data will never be used in any way different to that stated above without your explicit permission.
Cookies
Like most interactive websites this Company’s website [or ISP] uses cookies to enable us to retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are used in some areas of our site to enable the functionality of this area and ease of use for those people visiting. Some of our affiliate partners may also use cookies.
Links to this website
You may create a relevant link to any page of this website without our prior written consent. If you do create a link to a page of this website you do so at your own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above will apply to your use of this website by linking to it.
Links from this website
We do not monitor or review the content of other party’s websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or material appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. This Company will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.
Copyright Notice
Copyright and other relevant intellectual property rights exist on all text relating to the Company’s services and the full content of this website.
Communication
We have several different e-mail addresses for different queries. These, & other contact information, can be found on our Contact Us link on our website or via Company literature or via the Company’s stated telephone, facsimile or mobile telephone numbers.
This company is located in the Inland Empire region of Southern California, USA.
Force Majeure
Neither party shall be liable to the other for any failure to perform any obligation under any Agreement which is due to an event beyond the control of such party including but not limited to any Act of God, terrorism, war, Political insurgence, insurrection, riot, civil unrest, act of civil or military authority, uprising, earthquake, flood or any other natural or man made eventuality outside of our control, which causes the termination of an agreement or contract entered into, nor which could have been reasonably foreseen. Any Party affected by such event shall forthwith inform the other Party of the same and shall use all reasonable endeavours to comply with the terms and conditions of any Agreement contained herein.
Waiver
Failure of either Party to insist upon strict performance of any provision of this or any Agreement or the failure of either Party to exercise any right or remedy to which it, he or they are entitled hereunder shall not constitute a waiver thereof and shall not cause a diminution of the obligations under this or any Agreement. No waiver of any of the provisions of this or any Agreement shall be effective unless it is expressly stated to be such and signed by both Parties.
General
The laws of the United States and California govern these terms and conditions. By accessing this website you consent to these terms and conditions and to the exclusive jurisdiction of the U. S. courts in all disputes arising out of such access. If any of these terms are deemed invalid or unenforceable for any reason (including, but not limited to the exclusions and limitations set out above), then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be severed from these terms and the remaining terms will continue to apply. Failure of the Company to enforce any of the provisions set out in these Terms and Conditions and any Agreement, or failure to exercise any option to terminate, shall not be construed as waiver of such provisions and shall not affect the validity of these Terms and Conditions or of any Agreement or any part thereof, or the right thereafter to enforce each and every provision. These Terms and Conditions shall not be amended, modified, varied or supplemented except in writing and signed by duly authorised representatives of the Company.
Notification of Changes
The Company reserves the right to change these conditions from time to time as it sees fit and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any adjustment to these terms. If there are any changes to our privacy policy, we will announce that these changes have been made on key pages on our site. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on our web site 30 days prior to these changes taking place. You are therefore advised to re-read this statement on a regular basis.
These terms and conditions form part of the Agreement between the Client and ourselves. Your accessing of this website and/or undertaking of a booking or Agreement indicates your understanding, agreement to and acceptance, of the Disclaimer Notice and the full Terms and Conditions contained herein. Your statutory Consumer Rights are unaffected.
Share
Facebook
Twitter
LinkedIn
Leave a Reply Cancel replyYou must be logged in to post a comment.
Translate
Blog Archives
Blog Archives
Select Month
December 2020  (1)
November 2020  (2)
October 2020  (1)
September 2020  (3)
August 2020  (2)
July 2020  (3)
June 2020  (2)
May 2020  (1)
April 2020  (2)
March 2020  (1)
February 2020  (1)
January 2020  (1)
December 2019  (3)
November 2019  (3)
October 2019  (1)
September 2019  (1)
August 2019  (1)
July 2019  (1)
June 2019  (1)
May 2019  (1)
April 2019  (1)
March 2019  (2)
February 2019  (1)
January 2019  (1)
December 2018  (1)
November 2018  (1)
September 2018  (3)
August 2018  (1)
July 2018  (1)
June 2018  (1)
May 2018  (2)
April 2018  (1)
March 2018  (1)
February 2018  (2)
December 2017  (1)
November 2017  (1)
October 2017  (3)
September 2017  (4)
August 2017  (2)
July 2017  (6)
June 2017  (5)
May 2017  (5)
April 2017  (8)
March 2017  (4)
February 2017  (4)
January 2017  (5)
December 2016  (7)
November 2016  (3)
October 2016  (4)
September 2016  (1)
August 2016  (2)
July 2016  (4)
June 2016  (5)
May 2016  (2)
April 2016  (3)
March 2016  (4)
February 2016  (4)
January 2016  (4)
December 2015  (3)
November 2015  (4)
October 2015  (6)
September 2015  (4)
August 2015  (4)
July 2015  (4)
June 2015  (7)
May 2015  (4)
April 2015  (5)
March 2015  (3)
February 2015  (5)
January 2015  (5)
December 2014  (3)
November 2014  (2)
October 2014  (8)
September 2014  (8)
August 2014  (8)
July 2014  (11)
June 2014  (10)
May 2014  (12)
April 2014  (9)
March 2014  (7)
February 2014  (8)
January 2014  (12)
December 2013  (8)
November 2013  (8)
October 2013  (10)
September 2013  (9)
August 2013  (6)
July 2013  (10)
June 2013  (9)
May 2013  (12)
April 2013  (14)
March 2013  (11)
February 2013  (9)
January 2013  (12)
December 2012  (9)
November 2012  (12)
October 2012  (12)
September 2012  (12)
August 2012  (11)
July 2012  (12)
June 2012  (12)
May 2012  (15)
April 2012  (13)
March 2012  (13)
February 2012  (12)
January 2012  (15)
December 2011  (13)
November 2011  (16)
October 2011  (14)
September 2011  (13)
August 2011  (14)
July 2011  (14)
June 2011  (15)
May 2011  (17)
April 2011  (15)
March 2011  (17)
February 2011  (17)
January 2011  (17)
December 2010  (11)
November 2010  (15)
October 2010  (17)
September 2010  (19)
August 2010  (19)
July 2010  (16)
June 2010  (22)
May 2010  (20)
April 2010  (23)
March 2010  (23)
February 2010  (19)
January 2010  (20)
December 2009  (19)
November 2009  (19)
October 2009  (22)
September 2009  (21)
August 2009  (20)
July 2009  (22)
June 2009  (17)
May 2009  (20)
April 2009  (22)
March 2009  (20)
February 2009  (20)
January 2009  (20)
December 2008  (17)
November 2008  (18)
October 2008  (23)
September 2008  (21)
August 2008  (21)
July 2008  (23)
June 2008  (21)
May 2008  (20)
April 2008  (22)
March 2008  (21)
February 2008  (21)
January 2008  (21)
December 2007  (17)
November 2007  (20)
October 2007  (23)
September 2007  (18)
August 2007  (23)
July 2007  (17)
June 2007  (21)
May 2007  (22)
April 2007  (21)
March 2007  (22)
February 2007  (20)
January 2007  (21)
December 2006  (16)
November 2006  (21)
October 2006  (22)
September 2006  (20)
August 2006  (23)
July 2006  (13)
June 2006  (22)
May 2006  (21)
April 2006  (22)
Toyota Fine-T (Fine-X)
carsalepoint: I believe it all depends on demand. If the demand will increase in the future pr...
Hydro Kevin Kantola: Part of the VW Group, Audi has signed a deal with Hyundai to share hydrogen fuel...
rikky7777: What happened with all the VW Hydrogen projects, I know they collaborated with B...
Hydro Kevin Kantola: Tweet from Keith Malone of the California Fuel Cell Partnership: "Automakers ear...
Sandeep Mall: This car is amazing!! have the latest features and plus an amazing look....
Advocates (41)
Celebrities (21)
Competition (32)
Conferences (36)
Critics (11)
Entrepreneurs (10)
Fuel Cells (151)
Green Hydrogen (11)
History (52)
Home Hydrogen Fueling (15)
Hydrail (81)
Hydrogen Aircraft (33)
Hydrogen and Fuel Cell Jobs (2)
Hydrogen Bikes (27)
Hydrogen Boats (27)
Hydrogen Buses (55)
Hydrogen Cars (419)
Hydrogen Economy (102)
Hydrogen Education (26)
Hydrogen Forklifts (31)
Hydrogen Fuel (8)
Hydrogen Fuel Distribution (43)
Hydrogen Fuel Production (263)
Hydrogen Fuel Storage (52)
Hydrogen Fuel Tanks (29)
Hydrogen Fueling Stations (114)
Hydrogen Gas Savers (33)
Hydrogen Highways (44)
Hydrogen Organizations (12)
Hydrogen Safety (15)
Hydrogen Scooters (21)
Hydrogen Trucks (26)
Hydrogen Vehicles (183)
Hyrail (16)
Infrastructure (110)
Myths (13)
News (63)
Political Issues (65)
Uncategorized (31)
© Copyright 2020, Hydrogen Cars Now. All Rights Reserved.
